# Karishma Jadavji

Location: Coventry, United Kingdom
Email: <a href="mailto:karishmajadavji@outlook.com">karishmajadavji@outlook.com</a>
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/karishmajadavji

#### **Personal Profile**

Self-motivated and versatile Software Development graduate from Coventry University with a Bachelor's and Master's degree. A goal-oriented individual pursuing a career in Web Development with a passion for creating attractive, interactive and, responsive websites and mobile applications, committed to high standards of user experience, usability and speed. Excels in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript development. Lends detailed knowledge of SEO to increase visibility.

I'm currently searching for a front-end developer role that'll give me exposure to using markup languages like HTML to create user-friendly web pages, collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability etc.

I recently completed my Masters in Software Development and was exposed to a wide range of cutting-edge technologies and programming languages, which have equipped me with the skills and knowledge necessary to succeed as a software developer. To end off my master's degree I decided to create a mobile application using Flutter and Dart on VS Code. Using APIs to bring to life the maps element in the application and MongoDB to store any information which was logged into the application.

## **Education**

# Coventry University MSc Software Development (Pass)

2021 - 2022

Core Modules

- · Software Architecture and Engineering
- Modern Web Technologies
- · Secure Design & Developments
- · Data-Intensive Systems
- · Mobile Platforms & Application Development
- Software Development Project
- · Computing Individual Research Project
- · Advanced Software Development & Frameworks

## **Coventry University**

# BSc Digital and Technology Solutions (Upper Second-Class Honours 2:1)

2018 - 2021

Core Modules

- Business and Project Principles
- · Security Applications
- · Software Design Principles
- · IT Infrastructure Applications

- · Hardware and System Design Principle
- Database and Web Applications
- · Mobile Application Development
- · Advanced Software Developmen

## **Girls College**

2012 - 2017

A Levels: Mathematics, Business Studies, Economics, English (C-D) IGCSEs: 8 including English and Mathematics (A-E)

# **Hard Skill**

- · Database and SOL
- Object-oriented programming (OOP) languages
- Integrated development environments (IDEs)
- CSS3
- · HTML5
- · Cloud Computing
- · Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- · Git version control
- GitHub
- · Apache HTTP Server
- · JavaScript
- · MySQL
- · DevOps
- Flutter and Dart

## **Soft Skills**

- · Communication
- · Teamwork and Collaboration
- Time Management and Organization
- · Emotional Intelligence/ Empathy
- · Problem Solving/ Critical Thinking
- Creativity
- · People Skills and Management
- · Self-Awareness
- · Accountability
- Adaptability
- · Project management

# **Employment History**

# The Farmhouse Coventry, Coventry | Bar Manager

Aug 2020- Dec 2021

#### Key Responsibilities

- · Interviewing and recruiting new employees.
- · Responsible for conducting performance reviews.
- · Training junior team members whilst providing opportunities for growth and development
- · Overseeing schedule allocation and Rota's for all staff, ensuring the bar is operational.
- · Carrying out regular stock reviews and overseeing inventory management on behalf of the team.
- · Understanding individual customer requirements and working to meeting said requirements.
- · Implementing health and safety, first aid, hygiene and fire safety knowledge
- · Managing staff performance through monitoring punctuality, attendance, and customer service.

# The Farmhouse Coventry, Coventry | Senior Waitress

Jan 2019 - Aug 2020

# Key Responsibilities

- · Supervising and supporting the development junior team members.
- · Providing support to the Supervisor in ensuring all aspects of the restaurant is operating efficiently.
- · Delivering excellent standards of service in a friendly and professional manner to our customers.
- To assist in the set up if the restaurant before service, ensuring all required items are stocked and ready.
- · To deal efficiently and courteously with all guest queries.
- Ensuring the restaurant environment is always maintained and cleaned to a high standard.
- Excellent knowledge of restaurant menus to be able to offer guidance and make recommendations.

# Coventry University, Coventry | Student Ambassador

Sep 2018- Sep 2021

# Key Responsibilities

- · Acted as a friendly point of contact guiding visitors around the university
- · Discussed the university's courses, facilities, accommodation, and city

# Languages

English - Fluent Gujarati - Fluent Urdu - Native

Hindi - Native

Punjabi - Beginner